{
    "id": "6439859d61c64e22a92cba3f12f40afc",
    "title": "Verbs And Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Do you believe ..................... ghosts?",
            "description": "We use the preposition 'in' after the verb believe. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "567ae911c79844338dfb76e14601c2f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She spent years caring ..................... her sick husband.",
            "description": "To care for somebody is to look after them.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ee051629ce349ab871edd92031cd3c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "This spray will protect you ......................... most insects.",
            "description": "The verb protect takes the preposition from before an object. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5aba0a2a5c44320857864ad92a04f13"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has yet to recover .......................... his illness.",
            "description": "The verb recover takes the preposition from before an object.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "with",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "49a4a36acd8f4e488377e9816f05ea86"
        },
        {
            "question": "He won the national bravery award for saving his friend ..................... drowning.",
            "description": "We use the preposition from after the verb save. ",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "of",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "637c5ffa6a9f42ca80f3a2633967e3df"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard to succeed ........................ life.",
            "description": "Succeed is followed by the preposition 'in'. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dfdf28a55ed9499d8d2dff77ab82552f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't approve .......................... your conduct, young man.",
            "description": "Approve is followed by the preposition of.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "off",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c25dbd6dee6748deb66e9edc61795ddd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He suffers ..................... asthma.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e2e25025f8a94160be90f6bf3378fcbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "That shampoo smells ....................... jasmine.",
            "description": "Smell is followed by the preposition of.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bccff45b22fb4c70b681b04febae8de0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please don't make a noise. I want to concentrate ................... my studies.",
            "description": "Concentrate should be followed by the preposition on. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "on",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7113ca8f679f4a5db3841c2d14c29555"
        },
        {
            "question": "My husband and I can't agree ....................... anything but we love each other.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5806339928f34c3f96d966b30b48967a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please refer ......................... the glossary for more information.",
            "description": "Refer is followed by the preposition to. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8e8f4c6554cd4ecaa78bd21ccbffc375"
        }
    ]
}